coupons7.net 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy | CouponDiscountPromo.com

This is the Privacy Policy of CouponDiscountPromo.com, Inc. (“CouponDiscountPromo.com” or “us” or “we”). Our Terms of Use, which incorporates by reference this Privacy Policy, governs your use of our online services, any content or information therein, the CouponDiscountPromo.com website, any sub domains of CouponDiscountPromo.com, and any other website pages on which services are provided by us (collectively, the “Site”).

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality coupons and deals for products and services with integrity in dealing with our users. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and store the personal information you provide to us.

Please read the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy carefully. Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy may be modified by us from time to time. Any modifications we make will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site and the effective date of the latest version of the Privacy Policy will appear on this page. It is your responsibility to regularly check the Site to determine if there have been changes to the Terms of Use r the Privacy Policy and to review the changes.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit the Site, you may provide us with two types of information: information you actively choose to disclose (“Active Information”) and information collected in a way not visible to you on an aggregate, anonymous basis as you and others browse our Site (“Passive Information”).

When we refer to “personally identifiable information”, we mean information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number, or email address. Sharing personally identifiable information with us is entirely optional.

#### No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13

The Site is not intended for use by anyone under 18, except with the explicit permission and under the supervision of a parent or guardian who accepts full legal responsibility for the minor’s use. No person under 13 should disclose information on this Site. We don’t knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from children under 13.

Please note that if you grant consent for your child to use CouponDiscountPromo.com Services, this will include such general audience communication services as e-mail, instant messaging, and SMS text messaging. Parents can change or revoke the consent choices previously made, and review, edit or request the deletion of their children’s personal information. Thus, if a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us, to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

CouponDiscountPromo.com encourages all of its parental coupologists to talk with their children about communicating with strangers and disclosing personal information online.

#### Active Information You Choose to Provide

You may choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, mobile telephone number, and postal address, to register with the Site and to receive coupons by email or other services or information. You may also choose to provide your Zip code on the Site to receive information about products and services in your area.

#### Passive Information We Collect

Our Site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” to collect information about how our Site is used. Passive Information gathered may include your Internet service provider, browser type, operating system, the date and time of visits, the Site pages viewed, time spent at our Site, and the sites visited just before and just after our Site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit “cookie” information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the “Help” section of your browser to correctly do so. If you elect to turn off cookies, however, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site and your use of some portions of the Site may be affected.

#### What is a Cookie?

Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

#### How Do We Use the Information Collected?

Active Information

We will use the Active Information you provide us to deliver the content, features, advertising, services, or information you request. If you provide your email address, we may send you information or other messages related to your activities on the Site or about our services. We may retain the Active Information you provide and a record of the service or information provided. Any Active Information retained would be used to assist the delivery of the content, features, advertising, services, or information you requested, and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online.

We may use the Active Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our Site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you will find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please contact us. When you send us a message, we retain the content of the message, your email address, and any information you may provide to us, including your experience with the Site, and your contact preferences, as well as the response we send back to you. This helps us manage any follow-up questions you may have, measure how effectively we address your concerns, and improve the Site.

We may share Active Information with persons we employ directly or as contractors or agents at our direction, for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer services such as support, and making available other product or service offers or deals we think may be of interest to you. If we are acquired by another company, your personally identifiable information will be shared with our new owner, but it will remain subject to the terms of the then-applicable privacy policy or another set of terms if you agree to them.

Passive Information

We use Passive Information to enhance and design our Site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use, and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our Site, when they visit and how they use our service. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis and we do not connect any of this information to your email address or other personally identifiable information However, Passive Information may result in your viewing of particular content, features, advertising, services, or information based on your user habits or your viewing on our Site. We may also allow third parties to place cookies on our Site so we can help enhance your online experience after you leave our Site.

#### Your Information and Links to Other Web Sites

This Site contains links to other websites not owned by us that may have different privacy practices from ours. We aren’t responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy doesn’t apply to information collected by those sites. You should read those sites’ privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you choose to visit or shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before navigating.

#### Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties

We may share with third parties, such as advertisers on our Site or other website operators, anonymous, aggregated information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns. We may use your IP address and share it with third parties to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage the Site, and to enhance the Site based on usage pattern data.

#### Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law

We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services.

#### Protection of your Personally Identifiable Information

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information or Passive Information, we use reasonable efforts to secure the information you provide. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information, we can’t be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

Communications you may have with us via email or U.S. Mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.

#### International Users

This Site is hosted and operated in the United States of America. Those who access or use the Site from other jurisdictions do so at their own choice and risk and are solely responsible for compliance with local law. Please note that the personal information you submit to our Site will be transferred to and stored in the United States to be processed by us so we can provide this Site to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

If you are not a resident of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal information outside your home jurisdiction, and that we may store your personal information in the United States. Please note that the level of legal protection provided in the United States or other non-European countries in which you may access our Site may not be as stringent as that under European Union privacy standards or the privacy laws of some other countries, possibly including your home jurisdiction.

#### Contacting CouponDiscountPromo.com About Your Information or Information You Receive

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct you information, please contact us.

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use or disclosure of your personally identifiable information, please contact us.
